yourpfpro.com 2013-12-08

# Your Personal Finance Pro - Personal Financial Advice for Young Professionals

[Home](http://yourpfpro.com/) » Disclosures and Privacy Policy

## Disclosures and Privacy Policy

**Disclosures**  
“Please note that www.yourPFpro.com has financial relationships with some of the merchants mentioned here.  www.yourPFpro.com may be compensated if consumers choose to utilize the links located throughout the content on this site and generate sales for the said merchant.”

**Privacy Policy**

**www.yourPFpro.com** takes your privacy seriously. This privacy policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it.

**Routine Information Collection**

All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

Where necessary, **www.yourPFpro.com** uses cookies to store information about a visitor’s preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content.

Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies.

**Controlling Your Privacy**

Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms.

**Special Note About Google Advertising**

Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services. Learn how to [opt out of Google’s cookie usage](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

**Third Party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, check out

**Contact Information**

Concerns or questions can be directed to [yourPFpro at gmail dot com](mailto:youremail@youremail.com) for further clarification.

This blog is for informational purposes only. Any advice given does not constitute a relationship and is by no means fact. The information and advice given on this site is only an opinion and should be confirmed with a finance or tax professional.
